[SPEAKER_01]: So, let's talk about hindrances in relation to the wild animal.
[SPEAKER_01]: We talked about the fetters last time.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, what do hindrances do?
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, they hinder, but, I mean, more specifically, or differently described,
[SPEAKER_01]: Why are they particularly... well, why do they pertain to the wild animal, not to you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's also described as corruptions of mind, weaknesses of wisdom.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: What does it do?
[SPEAKER_02]: What does the hindrance do to the animal, the wild animal?
[SPEAKER_01]: What does it do to... That's just wildness.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: What does it do to the... to your experience as a whole?
[SPEAKER_01]: Why is it... What does the hindrance do to the relationship of... between you and the wild animal?
[SPEAKER_03]: Obscures it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which part?
[SPEAKER_03]: The relationship.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which part of it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I suppose the access, like the capacity to access.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: The wild animal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it obscures the wild animal.
[SPEAKER_03]: It obscures the space in between.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And makes it muddy, makes it cloudy, makes it colored.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, makes it overlooked, underlooked, over-intended, under-intended.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, what would be the first and foremost thing you would do in regard to any hindrance then, to not fall into overlooking the mind, underlooking it, missing it?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's killing the precepts, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_01]: More, more specifically now.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all taken for granted that you're already doing that, because you wouldn't be seeing the mind otherwise.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I mean, directly in relation to the hindrances.
[SPEAKER_01]: What can you do when the hindrance is present, the mind is obscured?
[SPEAKER_01]: How do you get it back?
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't act out of the hindrances.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't act out, that obviously would prevent things from getting worse, but it would still not necessarily remove the hindrance.
[SPEAKER_03]: And at the same time, which is also not immediately removing the hindrance, but you don't try to directly get rid of the hindrance.
[SPEAKER_03]: The hindrance, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because that would... What is those... what do those two things have in common?
[SPEAKER_01]: So, not acting out of the hindrance and not trying to directly remove the hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's the common thread?
[SPEAKER_01]: For both.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, why would you be acting out of a hindrance?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's... let's ask like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because you don't want to enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, because it's pressuring you and it's painful.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why would you want to be trying to get rid of the hindrance?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's not wanting to enjoy the pressure of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, both types of actions would really be rooted in hindrance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, that's the first thing you have to do if you want to get back to seeing your mind.
[SPEAKER_01]: Make sure that no act by body, speech or mind is rooted in hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, how do you make sure that?
[SPEAKER_01]: How do you make sure that?
[SPEAKER_01]: How do you do that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because whatever you want to attempt to do, is rooted in hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, what do you do then?
[SPEAKER_03]: The basic thing is to question the motivation, the intention behind whatever you are doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that will reveal it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But what does that lead to then?
[SPEAKER_01]: How do you then address the actual... because the hindrance is still there in the way, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you're still not revealing the mind.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or, as I said, you're not making it worse.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're still not revealing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why?
[SPEAKER_01]: So, whatever you attend to,
[SPEAKER_01]: will be coming out of hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: How do you bypass that?
[SPEAKER_01]: What is a single factor that would remove the hindering aspect of a hindrance?
[SPEAKER_00]: What is a single thing you can actually develop?
[SPEAKER_03]: Correct attention.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is the single reason that you're hindered.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's the single reason that everything you attend to is rooted in hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because without yoniso of your manasikāra, the yoniso of your manasikāra becomes a hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, although you're attending this and that and counterpart and stuff, all of... yoniso of that is the hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you want to push the yoniso further, where it's not the hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where is the mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: So, through not acting out of the pressure of the hindrance, you stay on the level where you know the mind is, even if you're not seeing it, and then balancing the womb, the inside of whatever's being attended, pushing for that perspective, but for that context, and the mind's there.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is what the mind will be.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, although then the tendency to the hindrance might be still present, and if you distract yourself from yoniso manasikāra, you become hindered again.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you cannot be hindered for as long as yoniso manasikāra is established.
[SPEAKER_01]: Impossible.
[SPEAKER_01]: Doesn't matter the amount of the pressure of the hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: But now that we got it out of the way, yes, not allowing pressuring images to take the center stage would be one way of re-establishing the balance.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not acting out out of the body, speech, or mind, not giving in to the pressure would be another way of re-establishing the balance.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the reason is you have to know that you have to be seeing past the hindrance through it to be unhindered, not to remove it or deal with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you easily, kind of, especially when it gets into these subtler levels, would fall into, kind of, a tendency, that's still there to some degree, to try to address it.
[SPEAKER_01]: As if, like, no, no, no, if I remove this, the mind will be seen.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: The mind is not seen, not because of the hindrance, but because your attention chose to rest on the hindrance, indirectly, as the basis.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, that needs to be bypassed.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's not something you can directly attend to.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, it's through that peripheral knowledge of what you're attending, that's what you then have to work on and keep looking further, to contain the hindrance rightly and to not be hindered by it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then also see, like as I said before, sometimes, if desire to see the mind is too strong, well, that will be the reason you won't be seeing the mind.
[SPEAKER_01]: If the intention, if the craving is too determined to see it, that will be the reason for obscuring it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, that's why goes hand... yoniso manasikāra goes hand in hand with knowledge.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, if you're not overdoing it, what you're left with is... well, you know that the space in between is there, whether you attend to it or not, whether you know it... whether you're aware of it or not, it has to be there.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, that knowledge already... already establishes a degree of balance.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, of course, within that, you're going to have more subtle pressures coming up, but the principle remains the same.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whereas knowledge has to be developed to the point where it becomes unshakable, regardless of what's being forced, what's forcing itself in between, to obscure it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, that's why mindfulness is always the basis of like, well, you can be doubting and not seeing the mind and all of this, but fundamentally, you recollect the basic context and then you know, okay, well, it is within this.
[SPEAKER_01]: It cannot be outside of this.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, just retrace your steps in that manner.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you don't want to be dealing with hindrances yourself.
[SPEAKER_01]: You want to be, basically, setting up
[SPEAKER_01]: The mind to deal with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The animal.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you set it up by not taking it at face value and acting out and trying to counter it or get rid of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then your work is, while the hindrance is pressuring you, to increase the depth of your yoniso, let's put it that way, so that the mind is discerned in regard to the hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not like, okay, it's gone, now I can go back to the mind.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: The mind needs to learn.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the mind's problem, which obviously makes it your problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, first, you don't act out of it, so you don't fall into a trap.
[SPEAKER_01]: Second, you recollect, you remember, you revisit the fact that the mind has to be there, even if it's not seen, and that it should not be seen at the expense of removing a hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: It should be seen through the hindrance, so that both are there, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's how the mind gets to know about hindrances and the problem of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, exactly, there won't be hindrances anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Checking on your intentions, it's another way of regaining, re-establishing the balance.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, what... why am I...
[SPEAKER_01]: Trying to to re-establish the balance of the mind now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it because I'm not seeing it, really?
[SPEAKER_01]: Or because I was pressured by something and I'm just needing to deal with it?
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's like, oh, well, that's why I won't be balancing it rightly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I'm acting out of such such an intention.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, being able to see yourself doing things... Yeah, that's always... that step is the first one and it never disappears, it never ceases.
[SPEAKER_01]: You always have to be able to see yourself doing or not doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: While you're doing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: While you're doing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before or after.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because it's said, it's said in the dosuttas, we mentioned it before as well, in the talks, like when agreeable perceptions come up, wrongly, not attending them with yoniso, they are hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: When disagreeable perceptions come up, absence of yoniso, they are a hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, if they're attended with yoniso, those things remain.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the hindering aspect that's gone.
[SPEAKER_01]: You want to bring up the animal and clarify it while being pressured.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's how you deal with it rightly.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's how the animal learns to calm down in regard to it and not be agitated by the presence of hindrances towards these certain directions of action and so on.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then you can clearly see, ah, the possibility of that hindrance is between the two of us.
[SPEAKER_01]: As in, the animal is hindered and I don't see it on account of it if I keep... well, you won't be seeing it because you end up acting out of it and not paying attention to your actions anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if you don't act out of it, it doesn't matter how obscure the animal is, you can always recollect the knowledge that it has to be there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, you can then, on top of that, recollect the knowledge that you shouldn't be trying to get rid of the hindrance that brings it even closer to the animal.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, you can recollect the knowledge that
[SPEAKER_01]: Attending through the hindrance brings up the animal while the hindrance is there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because is the hindrance felt?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who's feeling the hindrance?
[SPEAKER_01]: You or the animal?
[SPEAKER_00]: The animal.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Clarify the feeling of the hindrance, you got back the image of the animal.
[SPEAKER_00]: So the only thing you have to get rid of is the action?
[SPEAKER_01]: On your part, yes, and the ignorance on the animal's part.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, that's, I mean, like, it's the... it's about what you do, but then also you gotta now teach the animal the right course of action as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: To not resist it, to not... not try to get rid of it, to not, as I said, be agitated by the presence of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: They would then push you... try to push you towards action.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, yes, so animal feels.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't doubt that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't doubt the feeling.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can doubt whether the animal feels or not.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, if you would have not acted out of the pressing hindrance, if you would have maintained the context of yoniso and nisigāra, you would have recollected what's being felt there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the animal feeling the hindrance that you are now correctly attending all of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, simply by feeling the hindrance, the animal is revealed.
[SPEAKER_01]: And true feeling.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't stop feeling it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, okay, so it's the animal that needs to deactivate itself, calm down, basically, to the extent that it has been agitated by the hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's my task.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not to remove the hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's to calm the animal while the hindrance is there, repeatedly, until it basically stops being agitated by it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And when the animal is not agitated by the five hindrances, what happens then?
[SPEAKER_01]: What did the sutra say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Jhāna.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your mind is luminous.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's safe.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's secluded from unwholesome states.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, the animal... you seclude the animal not by hiding it in a dungeon, but by teaching it to remain immovable towards the fire.
[SPEAKER_01]: And when it's fully trained and immovable, you recognize, oh, it's actually quite secluded from anything that used to bother or agitate it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then you feel relieved on account of it, because there's no work for you there now.
[SPEAKER_01]: You could genuinely relax, as if you just paid a big debt.
[SPEAKER_01]: As if you just crossed a massive desert and relieved that everything's fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: As if you were just released from a jail where you were constantly under worry.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then the animal is factually calm, luminous, unobstructed, trained.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you still have perceptions coming up, thinking and pondering.
[SPEAKER_01]: But none of those come from a place of hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: They will try.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're trying.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the animal is equally immovable.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, none of that can come in between.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, again, as I said, it was through agitation of the animal that these things will be placed in between.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what Buddha did say, I think, in one of the suttas, that the first jhāna is besetted by the perceptions of sensuality.
[SPEAKER_01]: But not as a hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: Still trying to get you... Well, the thoughts, they still have their own habits.
[SPEAKER_01]: And for as long as, you know, especially, say, if the animal is
[SPEAKER_01]: Freshly come, recently come, there's still going to be matters and habits trying to, like, test that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you don't battle those things.
[SPEAKER_01]: You battle teaching the animal.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's your work.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not, not removal of these things that come up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because they are the problem only because the animal is agitated.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ayoniso manasikāra, basically.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's coming with, or seen through,
[SPEAKER_03]: It really doesn't matter what...
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't matter, because there is no... no obscuring takes place, because you remain... Detached.
[SPEAKER_01]: Detached.
[SPEAKER_01]: You remain sort of a recipient of the extent of the animals and your position there, and everything else that comes up, it's within that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, inevitably, you know, you would be, to some degree, falling into acting out of the hindrances.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's, that's the point.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, it's not like... Because, see, it can, it can feel like a daunting task.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, oh, these hindrances keep coming, and I have to keep dealing with them every time, and...
[SPEAKER_01]: But really, you don't deal with them.
[SPEAKER_01]: You only deal with them to the extent that you've been acting out of them, or they've been thinking about acting out of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that you need to stop, but then you realize, I don't need to deal with the hindrance.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just need to teach the animal to not be agitated and involved with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then the hindrance falls off, in a sense of the animal sort of is immovable, so it doesn't really matter if something is in between or not.
[SPEAKER_01]: There is no agitation.
[SPEAKER_01]: The animal does not go in hiding.
[SPEAKER_00]: In between, meaning, like, you're going around the rest of your day, you're not thinking, you know, about the animal, but that doesn't matter because you know that it's accessible.
[SPEAKER_01]: Depends.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you're going around your day mindfully, with clear awareness and comprehension, and the animal is always the background of your experience, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if you're going around because you're pressured by hindrance to go around, then it matters.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then you're acting out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it might be slightly, slightly tangential, but it's reminding me of something you were saying recently-ish, in regard to, like, teaching the animal how to not be
[SPEAKER_03]: How to be immovable in regard to hindrances.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because any hindrance, I'm going to paraphrase what you said, but any hindrance will have, like, one end of it is a sense of, like, pressure or some kind of itch, let's say, and it will have some image associated with it that, like, the animal
[SPEAKER_03]: What is associating with that itch or that kind of... it wants... it kind of corresponds to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, you are asking, like, what is the relationship or is there a relationship between the sense of pressure and the image that it wants to kind of land on and wants to go for?
[SPEAKER_03]: And the point is that there's no relationship at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a completely... Gratuitous association.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so then you are asking, like, so... And if there weren't... that's... it's completely gratuitous.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is no possible... there's no relationship at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's only kind of...
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it keeps feeding itself.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you keep taking it for granted.
[SPEAKER_01]: You keep taking it for granted.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, then, you were asking, like, so, how do you disassociate stuff?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so, how do you disassociate the images that want to take the center stage?
[SPEAKER_01]: Say, when you're pressured by hindrance of ill-will and images of anger towards person or whatever want to occupy, want to
[SPEAKER_01]: Activate your mind.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, how do you disassociate those images from that pressure?
[SPEAKER_00]: By not attending to them.
[SPEAKER_01]: What does that mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: Can I attend to something else?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I can distract myself from them?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well...
[SPEAKER_00]: If you're trying to get... if you're attending to something else on account of trying to get rid of the pressure, then that's obviously...
[SPEAKER_01]: So, how do you do then?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, there's a difference between... because that is being hindered, that is acting out of the pressure, but it is possible to...
[SPEAKER_01]: So, what's the difference between not attending and distracting yourself?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you have to include the pressure in that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then not attend to what?
[SPEAKER_00]: The image that is...
[SPEAKER_01]: So, those images are still there?
[SPEAKER_01]: As a blur.
[SPEAKER_01]: As a blur, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, you're right, but I want you to clarify it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because if you say, don't attend to them, aha, okay, so I'll attend to something else, at the expense of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, yeah, don't attend to them to the extent that you would be involving yourself with them.
[SPEAKER_01]: But not like, don't attend to them, get rid of them and replace them with new sets of images.
[SPEAKER_01]: You want to disassociate, and you can't disassociate if you remove the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you make sure they don't take the center stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: They remain there as a blur, but you're not feeding the association of specific images with centrality, specific images with your will.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you're really... like, I found that a very good... or, like, it's an important distinction, because, like, as a blur, like you were saying, you know, you can know
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly what...
[SPEAKER_03]: Even without sharpening it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Without focusing on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know exactly what it will be.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you don't even need to kind of... Look into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look into it to any extent.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, that's all you need to kind of keep it on that level.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there will be no possible continuance of that association.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's that middle ground that people tend to overlook.
[SPEAKER_01]: When the Buddha says, you know, he obliterates, he gets rid of the thoughts, that's how you do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You do it to the extent that you would be feeding them, but you don't do it to the extent of just replacing them with something else, because, well, you're just creating new thoughts.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now you're dependent on and you don't recognize where your input is.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he gave countless similes, you know, like the... how to do it rightly.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like that the turtle and the jackal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, the turtle is not in no position to chase the jackal away, but it is in a position to not extend its limbs out where the jackal would bite it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, the jackals remain there, waiting for its opportunity, but the turtle does not cross the line, does not reach out, and then the jackal leaves.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's how those blurring, blurred thoughts will leave you eventually.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not because you countered them through a perfect management technique, but through exactly not allowing them the center stage, which was your responsibility.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, that's why when the suttas describe getting rid of the stuff, they say you get rid of it through not welcoming, not delighting.
[SPEAKER_01]: And as I was saying, eh... back then, even without allowing the specific images to crystallize in your mind,
[SPEAKER_01]: While it's still the pressuring blur, you know exactly what images will be crystallized if you were too loud, even without even to think about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that part is you're doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, so no, I will remain enduring the pressure on the right level.
[SPEAKER_01]: I shall have the blurring possibilities waiting to be attended to and crystallized into more, but I won't do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I won't lose the sight of the peripheral, I won't lose the sight of the right context, I won't lose... whatever, wherever you're anchored.
[SPEAKER_01]: You won't lose the sight of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's your work, to that extent.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, yeah, it would be great if they don't come up in the first place.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you're in no position to make such a demand.
[SPEAKER_01]: And acting out of desire to not having come in the first place means overreaching for the jackal to chase him away.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then he bites you.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you remain hooked and trapped.
[SPEAKER_01]: And even when the Mahārāja was describing the Buddha, he said, for six years, he followed him closely, followed his eye, everything, every sense, every thought, to see if he can find an opening that he reaches out.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he couldn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then he gave up.
[SPEAKER_01]: And see, another layer to that, now in the context of this.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, by not overly reaching out, trying to get rid of things, by not distracting yourself, you remain feeling the pressure and the blur.
[SPEAKER_01]: In other words, you remain with the animal, even if you don't think it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because that which is felt on that level of pressure is what animal feels.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the animal's feeling.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that will eventually become apparent.
[SPEAKER_01]: You won't feel like it's animal's feeling, but that is where the animal is.
[SPEAKER_01]: What animal is.